Guide to the Planners Network records, 1975-2006.
Planners Network records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Planners Network records, 1975-2006.
4054
Planners Network.
2 cubic ft.
Printed Materials, Publications, Reports, Research Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records of the organization and its various conferences, brochures and newsletters, from 1975 onward.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records of the organization and its various conferences, brochures and newsletters, from 1975 onward.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Planners Network.
Subjects:
City planning--Societies, etc.; City planning
INFORMATION FOR USERS
NOTES
Forms part of Progressive Cities and Neighborhood Planning Collections.
CONTAINER LIST
- 2004 NYC PN Conference Packet, 2004 (Box 1)
  Includes bio and photo of five "Progressive Planning Pioneers" - Linda Davidoff, Chester Ahartman, Ron Shiffman, Peter Marcuse, Walter Thabit
- Ithaca planning conference 1979, 1979 (Box 1)
  Various agendas, correspondence..
- PN Intro Letter, 2000 (Box 1)
- PN Confrence 12/86?, 1986-1988 (Box 1)
  Memos, correspondence, financial statemetn, and 111pp report on Dec 86 conference
- PN Annual conference 1996 at Pratt, 1996 (Box 1)
  1pp directions to conference site
- 1986 Conference materials in red binder, 1986 (Box 1)
  Agenda, list of participants
- Annual PN Conference 2000, 2000 (Box 1)
  Toronto materials
- Workinhg papers and case studies prepared for PN Conference, Pratt, 1996 (Box 1)
- PN 1996 attendees, misc papers, 1996 (Box 1)
- East St Louis Conference misc., 1995 (Box 1)
- Mailing lists (Box 1)
- "PN Historical", ca. 1979 (Box 1)
  Various memos, correspondence - Hartman, steering conmmittee coming out of the Ithaca conference. N.b.: a large forlder with several sub-topics -- needs to be reorganized
- Woring for a Decent Living - Lowell conference packet, 1999 (Box 1)
- Linking Citizen Action and Equity Planning - E St Louis Conf Packet, 1995 (Box 1)
- 1987 (Box 1)
  Misc memos and correspondence
- Chron 1988, 1988 (Box 1)
- Sue's secretarial, 1987 (Box 1)
- Misc 1986 (Box 1)
- Tax exempt form (Box 1)
  Pratt
- Incorporation process (Box 1)
- Tides/Pequod, ca. 2000 (Box 1)
  Foundations,m correspondence, support for 2000 conference and misc things.
- Planners Network, ca. 2002 (Box 1)
- Membership 2000-2002 (Box 1)
- INURA (Box 1)
- Misc. Lists (Box 1)
- Planners NetworkNew national Speakers Bureau, ca. 2001-2005 (Box 1)
  Announciement from Ken Reardon, Cornell
- Old Brochures (Box 1)
- PN 2001 Conference (payments, etc.), 2001 (Box 1)
- Old financial Reports 86-93 (Box 1)
- Reprint Info (Box 1)
- Budgets/Expense (98-00) (Box 1)
- Financial 1994 (Box 1)
- Habitat Ingternational Coalition, 1997 (Box 1)
- Steering Comm, 1994-1996 (Box 1)
- Steering Committee (Old), 1981-1982 (Box 2)
- Cert of Incorporation, 1997, 2002 (Box 2)
- Fannie Mae Foundation, 1998-2004 (Box 2)
- IRS 2003 (Box 2)
- IRS-Incorporation (Old), 1997-1998 (Box 2)
- Bylaws - Old, ca 1997 (Box 2)
- Student Chapters, ca. 2003 (Box 2)
  Misc memos and correspondence; list of e-mail addresses of contacts at various universities
- PN 1975 -- Nos. 1-2, 1975 (Box 2)
  The newsletter. Appears to include two copies of each, through 2006, Issue 168.
- PN 1976-- Nos. 3-6 (Box 2)
- PN 1977 -- Nos. 7-11 (Box 2)
- PN 1978 -- Nos. 12-16 (Box 2)
- PN 1979 -- Nos. 17-22 (Box 2)
- PN 1980 -- Nos. 23-27 (Box 2)
- PN 1981-- Nos. 28-31 (Box 2)
- PN 1982 --Nos. 32-37 (Box 2)
- PN 1983 -- Nos. 38-43 (Box 2)
- PN 1984-- Nos. 44-50 (Box 2)
- PN 1985 -- Nos. 51-55 (Box 2)
- PN 1986 -- Nos. 56-61 (Box 2)
- PN 1987 -- Nos. 62-67 (Box 2)
- PN 1988 -- Nos. 68-73 (Box 2)
- PN 1989 -- Nos. 74-79 (Box 2)
- PN 1990 -- Nos. 80-85 (Box 2)
- PN 1991 -- Nos. 86-91 (Box 2)
- PN 1992 -- Nos. 92-96 (Box 2)
- PN 1993 -- Nos. 97-102 (Box 2)
- PN 1994 -- Nos. 103-108 (Box 2)
- PN 1995 -- Nos. 109-114 (Box 2)
- PN 1996 -- Nos. 115-120 (Box 2)
- PN 1997 -- Nos. 121-126 (Box 2)
- PN 1998 -- Nos. 127-132 (Box 2)
- PN 1999 -- Nos. 133-138 (Box 2)
- PN 2000 -- Nos. 139-144 (Box 2)
- PN 2001 -- Nos. 145-149 (Box 2)
- PN 2002 -- Nos. 150-153 (Box 2)
- PN 2003 -- Nos. 154-157 (Box 2)
- PN 2004 -- Nos. 158-161 (Box 2)
- PN 2005 -- Nos. 162-165 (Box 2)
- PN 2006 -- Nos. 166-169 (Box 2)
- Misc. Letters and Documents (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
- Planners Network No.36-55, 1982-1985 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Planners Network No.56-79, 1986-1989 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Planners Network No.80-108, 1990-1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Planners Network No.109-126, 1995-1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Planners Network No.127-144, 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Planners Network No.145-155, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  No. 156 becomes Progressive Planning - The Magazine of Planners Network
- Progressive Planning No.156-161, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Progressive Planning No.162-169, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Progressive Planning No.170-177, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Progressive Planning No.178-180, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Planners Network Reader (Box 3, Folder 14)